http://www.kolinskyartbrushes.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for S3 Stores, Inc. websites. We take our obligations with regard to your personal information seriously, and have created this privacy policy to inform you of the information gathering and dissemination practices of this website. In wishing to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information-collecting practices and to notify you of:
what personally identifiable information (or third party personally identifiable information) of yours is collected from you through our website the organization collecting the information how the information is used with whom the information may be shared what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information the kind of security procedures that are in place to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under S3 Stores, Inc. control how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that S3 Stores, Inc. is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact us. Information Collection and Use S3 Stores, Inc. is the sole owner of the information we collect on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy statement. S3 Stores, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on this website. Membership When you make a purchase on our website, you choose to become a member. You provide the following information to S3 Stores, Inc.:
Your name Your email address Your billing and shipping address Your telephone number Your form of payment You choose your own member identification and password to use for all future purchases on the site. You choose whether or not you would like to receive electronic mailings from S3 Stores, Inc.
Ordering We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here, a user must provide his/her contact and other information, (name and shipping address, shipping information, and form of payment). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. Sharing S3 Stores, Inc. does not share your private information with other companies. However, we may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. These companies may collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested services. Cookies S3 Stores, Inc. sites employ web browser cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. S3 Stores, Inc. uses cookies to identify your visit session for customizing your user experience, for creating web site analytical data, and for Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google AdWords on third party websites. We use both session and persistent cookies. The website visitor may use features of their web browser to block or delete S3 Stores, Inc. cookies, cookies used for Google AdWords, and/or cookies used for Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Adwords from the user's hard drive or memory. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, and the user may not see advertising on third party websites with reminders and special offers. You can opt out of Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Adwords by visiting their website and following the instructions presented on the page. Usage Tracking S3 Stores, Inc. database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and # of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our guests. Aggregate Information S3 Stores, Inc. uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners of S3 Stores, Inc. to plan advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information. Surveys S3 Stores, Inc. may conduct surveys and other studies of its user base and make use of the results for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option. We reserve the right to disclose information provided by any user through a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed. Circumstances under which S3 Stores, Inc. would publicly disclose aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with partners and/or site users, business planning, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. Newsletters, Catalogs, Etc. From time to time users may be given the opportunity to "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, catalog, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Out of respect for our users' privacy we provide ways to opt-out of these communications. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Tell-A-Friend If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about us or an item on our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. S3 Stores, Inc. will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We do store the friend's email and they have an option to opt-out in the communication. Special Request Pages Our customers can use our special request pages to inquire about products that they cannot find on the website, for special orders for example. Personal information is gathered during this process, and is used strictly for the purposes of replying to user inquiries, billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your phone, email or address), or if a user no longer desires our services, we offer ways to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. Links This website contains links to other sites, whether owned or controlled by S3 Stores, Inc., or unrelated third parties. Please be aware that the privacy policies of those sites may differ from those of S3 Stores, Inc., and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by S3 Stores, Inc. Online Security S3 Stores, Inc. takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, we take steps to protect your information both online and offline. To secure site integrity, we employ measures, including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. When a PayPal / 2CheckOut order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the standard encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears in your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. PayPal / 2CheckOut uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information (like your credit card information) online. Offline Security and Privacy We do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, all employees are fully informed about our security and privacy practices and are dutifully updated as new policies are added or revised. They are regularly notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. In the event that S3 Stores, Inc. becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, we shall take reasonable measures which we deem appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about security on our websites, please contact us. Privacy Policy Changes In the event of any changes to S3 Stores, Inc. Privacy Policy, we will post the changes to this page and other places we deem appropriate, so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We use information only in accordance with the privacy policy under which that information was collected. If at any time we plan on using your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in this policy at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice to allow or disallow us to use your information in this manner. If you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. Last modified: 8-19-13
You recently viewed items
Departments
Accessories
Adhesives & Fasteners
Adhesive Tapes
(14)
Adhesive Sheets
(1)
Glue and Glue Dots
(39)
Clips
(1)
Stamps
(3)
Airbrush Supplies
Airbrush Additives & Mediums
(10)
Airbrush Compressors
(63)
Airbrushes
(92)
Airbrush Cleaning Supplies
(4)
Airbrush Paint
(6)
Airbrush Templates & Stencils
(4)
Airbrush Spray Booths
(15)
Airbrush Accessories
(396)
Refrigerated Air Dryers
(1)
Spray Guns
(25)
Airbrush Hoses & Connectors
(26)
Airbrush Bottles
(55)
Books & DVDs
DVDs
(105)
Books
(42)
Artist Paint Brushes
Acrylic & Oil Art Brushes
(254)
Watercolor Paint Brushes
(34)
Brush Washers & Cleaners
(4)
Decorative & Miniature Brushes
(8)
All Purpose Brushes
(14)
Paint Brush Organizers & Holders
(2)
Art & Craft Supplies
Decorative & Tole Painting
(28)
Gold & Metallic Leaf
(34)
Marbling Supplies
(3)
Transfer Papers & Image Transfer
(3)
Wood Crafts & Supplies
(24)
Stamping
(569)
Dies
(1713)
Decorative Stickers
(215)
Craft Embellishments
(2)
Stonework
(1)
Carving
(92)
Craft stencils & templates
(393)
Clay & plaster crafts
(43)
Painting Canvas
(15)
Hobby Gifts for Kids
(6)
Fabric Craft Supplies
(64)
Clips
(1)
Staplers & Staples
(1)
Cleaning Supplies for Craft Mishaps
(6)
Scrapbooking
(520)
Tools
(59)
Manual Sanding Products
(6)
Cardstock Colored Paper
(3)
Cutting Tools
Art Knives & Blades
(19)
Cutting Mats
(9)
Punches
(94)
Circle & Oval Cutters
(1)
Glass Cutters
(2)
Mat Cutters & Accessories
(3)
Paper Cutters & Trimmers
(17)
Scissors & Shears
(14)
Drafting & Architectural Supplies
Drawing Boards & Accessories
(1)
Modelling
(29)
Drafting Supplies
(1)
Architectural Supplies
(3)
Drawing Supplies
Pastels
(4)
Pencils
(28)
Pens
(19)
Charcoal & Graphite
(3)
Markers
(15)
Inks
(67)
Calligraphy Supplies
(1)
Easels
Studio Easels
(3)
Art Horses & Bench Easels
(1)
H-Frame Easels
(1)
Single-Mast Easels
(1)
Wall Mounted Easels
(2)
Aluminum & Metal Easels
(4)
Wood Easels
(5)
Display & Presentation Easels
(15)
Outdoor & Plein Air Easels
(12)
Educational & Instructional Materials
Color Charts & Color Wheels
(94)
Photography Supplies
Picture Framing Tools
(6)
Picture Hanging Hardware
(1)
Picture Frame Parts
(3)
Photo Mat Boards & Mat Cutters
(19)
Painting Supplies
Watercolor Paint Supplies
(23)
Spray Painting
(1)
Varnishes
(11)
Rubber Brayers
(10)
Acrylic Paint Supplies
(23)
Oil Paint Supplies
(266)
Priming & Surface Preparation
(13)
Encaustic Painting
(12)
Paint Accessories
(29)
Raw Materials
(353)
Chalks
(2)
Kids Painting Sets
(2)
Surface Preparation Supplies
(1)
Art Paper Pads
Cardstocks
(38)
Watercolor Papers
(2)
Drafting paper
(1)
Art Boards & Canvas
(13)
Cards, Greeting Cards, Envelopes & Postcards
(29)
Decorative Papers
(116)
Drawing Papers & Surfaces
(3)
Glassine & Barrier Papers
(1)
Mixed Media Papers & Pads
(2)
Pastel Papers & Surfaces
(6)
Printmaking Papers
(2)
Sketch Paper & Pads
(46)
Wood & Hardboard Panels
(41)
Paper Tools
(1)
Memory Planners
(1)
Decoupage Paper
(33)
Presentation Supplies
Exhibit & Display Systems
(1)
Print & Document Protectors
(1)
Art Pedestals
(67)
Hanging Clamps & Accessories
(1)
Brushes
Papercraft Supplies
Quilling Supplies
(6)
Decoupage Paper
(8)
Embossing Supplies
(141)
Scratchboard Supplies
(1)
Die Cutting
(25)
Constuction Paper
(1)
MDF Dimensional Art
(2)
Bundles
Rollers
(10)
Paper clinch
(2)
Twiggy
(1)
Scissors
(1)
(2)
(82)
Pencil Cases & Pouches
(4)
Furniture For Artists
(22)
Lamps & Accessories
(4)
Chalkboards & Whiteboards
(7)
Health and Safety in the Art Room
(187)
Art Cleaning Supplies
(9)
Transporting & Carrying Art Materials
(47)
Art and Craft Tracing Light Boxes
(4)
New Products
Embellishments
(295)
Stickers
(17)
Products
(58)
Manufacturer
(151)
Plus America
(5)
Art
(1)
General Crafts
(9)
Knitting
(1)
Wholesale
(1)
New Products
(2)
Painting Supplies
(285)
Brushes
(12)
Art & Craft Supplies
(13)
Art Paper Pads
(1)
Pet supplies
(1)
White boards
(7)
Accessories
(14)
Adhesives & Fasteners
(1)
Bundles
(5)
Magnets
(1)
Utility knives
(2)
Scissors
(2)
Glue tape
(15)
Led shelving
(1)
Led snap frame light boxes
(1)
Porta-trace light boxes
(2)
Boombowl™ collection
(12)
Decobreeze® fans
(31)
Decoflair® candles & home accents
(186)
Activated carbon
(8)
Aimed series air purifier
(1)
5000 air purifier
(5)
5000 dx mcs
(2)
5000 vog air purifier
(1)
6000 d
(1)
6000 dx
(1)
40 lbs activated carbon filter
(1)
5000 d air purifier
(1)
6000 d air purifier
(1)
$0-10
(1)
$25-50
(2)
$10-25
(7)
Craft gift card
(1)
Decor sand
(1)
1 lb - 5 lb
(1)
Colored sand
(4)
Flower drying art
(1)
Casting
(1)
Activ-tools
(4)
Kiln fired clay
(4)
Earthenware clay
(2)
High fire clay
(1)
Ceramics
(1)
Self-inking stamps
(399)
Alphabet
(13)
12.1
(46)
Extended-planning
(19)
Accessory-essentials
(146)
Mixmatch6.16
(15)
Regular-price
(18)
Scmambi
(23)
Funtional-accessories
(13)
Augustmarkdowns
(8)
Julymarkdowns7.28
(1)
Flash
(18)
Decorative-accessories
(9)
2020
(484)
Office-shop
(2)
Saleonsale7.2
(2)
1.13
(115)
11.29
(10)
Calendar refill
(9)
Cover_snap in
(3)
Big plans
(1)
Color_black
(2)
Color_gold
(1)
Color_blue
(1)
Bfpromo
(3)
Binding_disc bound
(114)
Colorful-rainbow-stickers
(6)
Decorative-stickers
(10)
4.23 markdown
(9)
Back-in-stock
(4)
Meal prep
(2)
Btssale7.17
(13)
Offsite
(1)
Sticker pack_multi accessory pack
(1)
Prayer
(1)
A-691
(11)
Academic
(1)
Bright
(1)
5.20 markdown
(3)
3 pack journal
(1)
A-684
(12)
1.20
(39)
11.21
(14)
12.10
(49)
2.14
(20)
Happy notes_notebooks
(1)
Custom
(5)
Fa-selfcare
(1)
Axs-storage-preview
(10)
Fall 2020
(13)
Fa-newfeatured
(1)
Comingsoon
(28)
Black artist cover
(3)
New!
(2)
Embossers
(83)
Wood mount stamps
(160)
Gifts + accessories
(34)
Craft + diy
(28)
Pencil cases & pouches
(54)
Markers
(50)
Colored pencils
(27)
Crayons & chalk
(79)
Big box™ school supplies
(6)
Spiral notebooks
(77)
Composition books
(59)
Rulers
(28)
Standard pencils
(45)
Specialty paper
(21)
Basic pocket folders
(95)
Filler paper
(30)
Safety scissors
(16)
Calculators
(21)
Craft glue
(29)
Coloring books
(98)
Index cards, guides & cases
(31)
1\
(42)
Glue sticks
(36)
All-purpose scissors
(22)
School supply kits
(32)
Dry-erase boards & accessories
(49)
Wireless notebooks
(13)
Pencil sharpeners
(58)
Construction paper
(16)
Invisible tape
(12)
Stick pens
(42)
Post-its & sticky notes
(37)
Novelty pens
(31)
Highlighters
(51)
Teaching tools
(14)
Craft paint
(10)
Erasers & correction supplies
(97)
Ring binder accessories
(44)
Novelty items
(1)
Paintbrushes
(14)
Permanent markers
(33)
Gel pens
(27)
Tape
(5)
Magnifiers
(14)
Journals & diaries
(16)
Clipboards
(20)
Document organization & protection
(30)
Mechanical pencils
(39)
Super glue
(8)
Activity books
(47)
Shipping & industrial tape
(18)
Dictionaries & thesauruses
(4)
1-1
(9)
Pen & pencil sets
(7)
Notebooks & composition books
(13)
Memo pads
(24)
Retractable pens
(13)
Name holders & lanyards
(16)
Filing supplies
(33)
3\
(9)
Charts & supplies
(11)
Markers & highlighters
(9)
Awards & incentives
(29)
Easel pads
(2)
Decorations
(10)
Office forms
(4)
Rubber bands
(10)
Pencil grips & toppers
(12)
Classroom & teacher supplies
(5)
Shipping & mailing supplies
(19)
1
(9)
Dowels, craft sticks & clothespins
(4)
Books & calendars
(2)
Money-handling supplies
(3)
Envelopes
(1)
Copy & printer paper
(7)
Book accessories
(17)
Math sets
(11)
Unicorn & mermaid
(1)
Hole punchers
(5)
Novelty pencils
(30)
Desk organizers
(1)
Educational workbooks
(3)
Pens
(5)
2\
(8)
Classroom crafts
(2)
Compasses
(6)
Folders & portfolios
(1)
Double-sided tape
(3)
Calendars
(1)
Locker accessories
(14)
Poster board
(2)
Boards & accessories
(9)
Protractors
(5)
Home school
(1)
Color paper
(3)
Mounting tape & squares
(3)
Labels
(8)
Paperclips
(14)
Staplers & accessories
(18)
Fashion pocket folders
(22)
Stamps & ink pads
(2)
Lead refills
(8)
Writing instruments
(2)
Legal pads
(8)
Three-ring binders
(1)
Tape dispensers
(4)
Pencils
(5)
5\
(1)
Push pins & thumbtacks
(7)
Glue
(2)
Glitter glue
(5)
4\
(2)
Reading glasses
(1)
Felt-tip pens
(5)
Decorative tape & dots
(1)
Signs
(2)
Arts & crafts books
(2)
Office supplies
(2)
Paper rolls
(1)
Stencils
(1)
16\
(1)
Artograph
(11)
Bfcm 2020
(7)
Laser designs
(1011)
12x12 overlays
(348)
Bling & shiny things
(218)
Chipboard albums
(351)
Chipboard quotes
(55)
Chit chat build a book
(136)
Fancy chipboard words
(181)
6 x 6 overlays
(5)
Templates
(62)
Military
(45)
Collection_mickey and minnie mouse
(3)
Collection_princess
(6)
Color_pink
(1)
School & office
(1)
Christmas HITS!
Instructor set
Pastels
(12)
Professional
(2)
Pastels
Professional
(43)
Drawing material
Pastels
(2)
Pavement pastels
(2)
Cotton
Diy
(1)
Oil paint
Prop65
(1)
Professional
(3)
Paint sets
(1)
Portfolio
Prop65
(1)
Casein
Professional
(1)
Milk-based paint
(1)
Gesso
Prop65
(1)
Acrylic
Gouache
(1)
Pan watercolor
Professional
(2)
Child
Drawing model
(1)
